Sun
Mon
Tues
Wed
Thurs
Fri
Sat
Yo.
Inu!
Izumi's out sick today!
Goals for the Week
This Month's Events
Jeez, not so loud. How do you
have so much energy this early?
Also, don't drop the "zuka."
I don't wanna hear that from a guy who
rolls up his sleeves when it's this cold.
Izumi messaged me this morning.
Sorry! Could you take notes for me?
Ok
Thanks
He asked me to take notes for him.
Oh, so you already knew?
I feel so left out.
Oh... Notes, huh?
He didn't say anything to me.
For some reason, my friend's
girlfriend sees me as a rival.
Shikimori's Not Just a Cutie
Shikimori's
Not
Just
a
Cutie
Shikimori's
Not
Just
a
Cutie
Shikimori's
Not Just a Cutie
Amusement Park
Shikimori-san might like it??
Get a reservation!!!
Get gifts for the family
Eat this!!
Inuzuka-kun
Keep warm and go to bed early!!
Inuzuka-kun!!
Please Help
I'm going to an amusement park with
Shikimori-san next week. Suggestions...?
#09  Innocence and Clumsiness
Why does this happen?
Does she think everyone who's ever
in Izumi's vicinity is her rival?
I guess it's true. Love really is blind.
Well, Neko and I hang around Izumi, too,
and she's never glared at us.
What?! Does she just hate me, then?!
Tell me, Nekozaki!
Not so close!
Look, she doesn't hate you, okay? You're fine.
Just today, Micchon was saying...
Inuzuka-kun is so nice.
He's always right there with
Izumi-san, helping him out.
Yeah, like in PE!
And he's always got his arm around
his shoulder. It looks like such fun.
And they eat lunch together every day...
Every day... together...
Micchon?
And Inuzuka-kun is the one he
asks to take notes for him.
I'd take better notes for him
than I take for myself!
Wow, she's a pain!
So that's how it is, huh?
He only asked me to take notes for him.
I mean, I don't think I'm doing
anything wrong, though.
Sheesh. That Izumi ought
to be ashamed of himself.
Hey, Inuzuka-kun...
Do you mind if I go to
Izumi-san's house with you today?
Erk!
Fine with me.
You said something before that, didn't you?
Bye-bye!
Adieu.
Should we have let those two go together?
Hachimitsu!
What?
I can't go since I have practice,
but I can't turn a blind eye to this!
Follow them!
I'm on it.
Hey, Shikimori.
Do you... like...
Look, she doesn't hate you, okay? You're fine.
Nah, never mind.
Okay.
Oh, there's somewhere I'd like
to swing by. Is that okay?
Sure, I guess.
As the Dry Season Comes, You Need Quick Results!!
Which one should I get?
Black HARD
Throat Drops
Ultra Propolis Blend
Contains 1,000mg
This one... or this one?
Yuzu and Honey Throat Drops
Contains 19% Yuzu Juice
Which one would Izumi-san like?
Is it worth agonizing over that much?
Which do you think he'd like?
Uh, the one on the right.
So thoughtless!
Then...
If it's between this one and this one...
Which would you pick, Nii-san?
Huh? Those aren't even throat drops.
Hey, that one has
grape-flavored ones in it!
Totally the left!
Wait...
Did you just call me "Nii-san"?
I-I-I...
I did not! Off to the checkout line!
Isn't that like calling your teacher "Mom"?
Here.
Huh? What're you talking about?
It's for you.
Huh? You didn't get that for Izumi?
The throat drops are for him.
These are for you.
Why?
You like grape, right?
What the heck are you planning?
Fine. You can't have them.
I'm sorry! You're super cool! I love grape!
I see.
All the mysteries have been solved.
The heck are you doing?!
Hachimitsu?
Hup.
The truth is, I was secretly following you.
Why, though?
What "mysteries" are you talking about?
I'm glad you asked.
Don't ignore me!
I have figured out Shikimori's heart.
H-Her heart?
M-My heart?
Shikimori-san.
You have an older brother, correct?
Y-Yes.
And you always talk to your friends about him.
Friend
You say you have trouble
being open with him
and end up treating him a bit coldly.
What's she talking about?!
I'm saying that you unconsciously
conflate Inu with your brother
and you just want his attention!
Wait, so all those times she's
treated me like a rival...
She was just going into youngest-child mode
and letting her possessiveness
show on the surface.
Nah, that can't be it.
Hey, Shikimori, you tell her.
Y-Yeah! I definitely don't think he
kinda talks and acts like my brother!
So you do, then.
Oh... So she doesn't actually hate me.
Although...
I can't say it really felt like she
just wanted my attention.
Oh, Inu...
Don't drop the "zuka."
You've got some good stuff there.
Give me one.
But still...
I don't feel that bad about it.
No way!
This was a gift from a cute little
attention-seeking baby.
Oho.
Well, I can't fault you for that.
What did you just call me?
I'm sorry! I went too far!
M-My back... gave out...
I hope Inuzuka-kun gets here soon.
My club has the day off today!
It's just you and me, Micchon!
This doesn't happen often, huh?
Izumi and Hachimitsu are both sick,
and I guess Inu's at work.
It has gotten awfully cold lately.
And our athletic festival's coming up.
I hope it'll be okay...
Oh, it looks like Izumi-san will be
back at school next week.
Yeah? Good for you, Micchon.
Izumi-san
The seasonal cold this year is terrible.
Please use a humidifier in your room so you don't dry out.
You might want to hang your wet towels up to dry, too.
Oh, and they say gargling helps to prevent dryness!
Have you taken your medicine?
Make sure you take your cold medicine, okay?
And keep warm, and wear a mask so you won't hurt your throat!
And eat foods that are soft, warm, full of moisture,
and easy to digest, like rice porridge.
Overprotective!!
Now you won't be lonely
going to and from school,
and you won't stay glued
to your phone all day.
I'm not glued to it!
Oh, yeah?
Hey, isn't that Kamiya?
Kamiya-san...
She's so slim.
She really does stand out,
even from a distance. Right, Neko?
Huh?! Neko?!
Hey, Kamiya! All by your lonesome?
When did she...
You never hold back at all, do you, Nekozaki?
Oh, you remember her, right?
From the Couple Numbers game.
Yes.
Shikimori-san, right?
Yep!
It's good to see you again, Kamiya-san.
Hey, wanna hang out with us?
Just kidding!
Hmm...
Sure.
Yeah, I didn't figure you'd...
You will?!
For a change.
Wh-Where shall we go?
Kamiya, is there anywhere you wanna hit?
Hmm, let me think...
Isn't this cute?
That's cute?
I don't get what sets her off!
They just keep playing
with those puppies...
The Latest
Newest Version ♥
Filters
Burst Mode
Let's take sticker photos!
Make a cool face!
Let's see how they came out.
What is this, a CD jacket?!
I'm going to the restroom!
You two have fun!
Shikimori-san, do you mind if I try that?
Looks fun!
How do you do this?
You've never played it before?
No.
See that moving part?
You try to match its timing.
When it's where you want it, press 1, and...
I missed. This is too hard.
I'll try, too.
Grab
Drop
Here.
No, you won those yourself.
It's okay.
I got them so I could give them to you.
Are you like this with everyone?
What do you mean?
Nothing. Never mind.
Now, I'll win something you want.
You don't have to do that.
It's fine.
I don't like just having things
done for me all the time.
Th-Then...
I wonder where they went.
I got it!
There. Now we're even, right, Kamiya-san?
I can't believe you got it
from that position...
You're good.
They're best buds all of a sudden!
I bet we could get that one, too.
Yeah, if we catch the string
and scoot it to the side.
Girls' Volleyball
Kamiya! Wanna go somewhere on the way home?
Sorry, Nekozaki. I'm in a hurry today.
Oh, okay. See ya later, then!
Later.
Hey, Nekozaki...
Maybe you shouldn't bother
inviting Kamiya anymore.
Huh? Why not?
Well, she's kind of a loner, you know?
She doesn't seem to like hanging out much.
And it's rude of us to make
her say no every time.
Yeah.
Is that really how she feels?
I've never seen Kamiya smile so much...
I'm back!
Looks like you're having fun!
What do you wanna do next?
What the heck?! Don't you think
you won too much stuff?!
Oh, that just... h-happened.
Look! A basketball court!
Let's play a little.
Hey, hey, hey!
We're about to use this court,
just so you know.
Why don't you, like, scram?
Oh...
I didn't know the court
required a reservation.
Y-Yeah, that's right!
This courts is reservation only!
And you should, like, obey the rules!
They're gals with morals...
Sorry about that.
Let's try somewhere else.
Like where?
Hold it!
We'd be willing to duke it out
for the right to use this court.
Frankly, playing one-on-one is, like, boring.
We just wanna play basketball with you.
Um...
Or are you scared you'll lose?
Very well. Shall we, then?
They seem good. Think we can win?
You're just letting them egg you on!
Well, if that's what we're doing,
I'll be the ref.
You're totally into this, huh?
I, like, love girls like you!
Just so you know, we played in the
regional tournament in middle school.
We're, like, not gonna lose.
Here!
Nice shot!
Way to go!
They're fast!
Here!
We're just, like, getting started!
We totally lost.
Like, who are they?
They really were good.
Talk about tenacious.
Your teamwork got the better of us!
You're, like, such good friends!
Friends...
Your teamwork was really good, too!
You know we gotta, like, take a pic now!
You guys better get in on this, too!
They're overwhelming...
Man, that was fun!
Well, see you at school tomorrow.
Yeah, see you tomorrow.
You too, Kamiya-san. See you.
Yeah.
Um, if it's okay with you...
It'll be as friends next time, okay?
Huh? But after all you just did
together, you're already—
Just be quiet for a minute.
Kamiya-san...
I'd love that.
Kamiya, you've changed.
Have I?
Yeah!
I mean, you looked like
you were having a blast!
I've never seen you smile so much before.
That didn't seem like me?
Well, I was surprised, but I was super happy!
I've always wanted to hang out
and have fun with you.
I learned tons of new stuff about you today.
Nekozaki...
Yeah?
Sorry about how I was before.
Huh?
Wh-What brought this on?
I mean...
You invited me out all the time,
but I always said no, remember?
Huh? Oh, don't worry about that!
I was the one being kinda pushy about it.
Sorry if I made you feel bad.
You're very kind, Nekozaki.
Huh? I'm just doing what I wanna do.
Actually, I'd say you're the nice one.
Too nice, even.
No, no...
No, no, no.
Anyway, what do you want to do, Nekozaki?
Remember what I said?
I just want to know more about you.
We're friends, after all!
You're right. You can ask me anything.
Did you say "anything"?!
Well, anything I can actually answer...
Uh, let me think... um...
Oh! What's your favorite sweet snack?!
That's it?
Sorry, but I don't really have one.
You're kidding!
I don't know what's good or whatever...
Actually, my taste buds are kinda weird.
Huh?
It feels rude, so I never told
anyone about it before.
Wow...
Yours is chocolate, right?
I can't believe you knew!
I'm glad.
Any other questions?
Uh, hang on a second...
Nothing's coming to me.
You can take your time thinking about it.
Okay.
Hey, do you know Izumi well?
You guys were together during
the cultural festival.
Yeah.
Oh! Did you know Izumi and
Micchon are going out?
Are they?
I guess you're not interested... in...
You know...
I never know what Kamiya-san is thinking.
She's so cool and good-looking!
She's not interested in other people.
I wish I had a body like hers.
I bet she wants for nothing.
She's gorgeous, and everyone admires her.
She's perfect!
She's a loner.
She's so cold. She never hangs out.
Hey, Kamiya...
You know how you never
used to smile like this?
You always seemed like you were hurting.
Who was it that changed you?
Sorry. I can't say.
I see.
I can't say, but...
There is someone who told me that
I should treasure what I feel.
I understand that now.
It doesn't matter if I'm hurt or tired.
I hope...
I can tell you someday.
Sure. I'll be waiting!
Oh, man! Here comes the train! Run!
Yeah.
Kamiya, you can take your time.
Keep discovering more of your own feelings.
And one day, when you find a way to deal
with them other than stifling them...
I hope...
I hope you'll smile from
the bottom of your heart.
Just kidding!
SEE YOU~